Finding Aid for the Collection of 78rpm Sound Discs PASC-M.0174
UCLA Library Special Collections
- General Collection, Series 1.
  - Popular Music Recordings, Subseries 1.
    - I Know Why, 1918; 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 10197, side 1
      Also composed by: Morgan.
    - I Love You, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 14170 A
      On label, "From "Little Jessie James"."
    - Idol Eyes, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 2975, side 2
      Also composed by: Hersher and Burke.
    - I'm Away From the World When I'm Away From You ('Cause You're All the World to Me), 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 1187 a
    - I'm Drifting Back to Dreamland, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 12088 B
    - In Babyland, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 10269, side 1
    - In the Land of Rice and Tea, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 2975, side 1
      Also composed by: Blese.
    - It's All Over Town, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 105, side 1
      Also composed by: Rudolf Friml.
    - Jalousie, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 23311 B
      Also composed by: Jacob Gade.
    - Just a Girl That Men Forget, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 12067 A
    - Just Because You're You That's Why I Love You, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 14033 B
      2 copies.
    - Kilima Waltz, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 10187, side 2
    - Linger Awhile, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 11329 A
      Also composed by: Vincent Rose.
    - Love (My Heart is Calling You), 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 12067 B
    - Makin' Faces at the Man in the Moon, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 5359 C, side 2
      Also composed by: Smith, Hoffman and Washington.
    - Marie, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 827 H, side 2
    - Maui Chimes, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 826 H, side 2
    - Me, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 1699 B
    - Me and the Man in the Moon, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 778 H, side 1
    - Mississippi Mud, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 694 H, side 2
    - Monte Cristo Jr. Medley, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 2751, side 1
      Flutter On By My Broadway Butterfly -- Sahara -- Monte Cristo.
      Also composed by: Schwartz and Bryan.
    - Morning Will Come, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 12066 B
      Also composed by: De Sylva and Conrad.
    - My Sunny Tennessee, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 3465, side 1
      Also composed by: Harry Ruby and Herman Ruby.
    - My Sweetie Went Away (She Didn't Say Where When or Why), 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 12061 A
      Also composed by: Handman.
    - No Escape, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 105, side 2
      Also composed by: Shefter. On label, "from the United Artists Release "No Escape".
    - Old Man Sunshine, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 660 H, side 2
      Also composed by: Dixon.
    - Old Time Waltzes, Part 5, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 14463
      On a Sunday Afternoon -- On the Banks of the Wabash -- Smarty! Smarty! Smarty! -- Auld Lang Syne.
    - Old Time Waltzes, Part 6, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: B 14463
      School Days -- Wild Irish Rose -- Sweet Adeline -- Good Night Ladies.
    - One and Two and Three and Four, Rock-A-Bye, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 2751, side 2
      For Johnny and Me -- The Boys Who Won't Come Home.
      Also composed by: Layton, Al Von Tilzer, and Himlton.
    - Pal of My Dreams, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 12088 A
    - La Paloma, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: C 1167 b
    - Roly Boly Eyes Medley, 1918; 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 10111, side 1
      Dippy Doodlums -- A Bungalow for Two.
      Also composed by: Greenberg
    - Ruspana, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 2712, side 2
    - See Saw Medley, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 10111, side 2
      See Saw -- When You Dance.
    - Seven or Eleven (My Dixie Pair O' Dice), 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 14120 B
    - The Sneak, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 14033 A
    - Some Sunny Day, 1921; 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 9223, side 2
    - Somebody Stole My Gal, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 11329 B
    - The Song I Love, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 811 H, side 2
      Also composed by: Brown, Henderson and Conrad.
    - Sunshine Alley, 1921; 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 9223, side 1
    - Sweet Ella May, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 694 H, side 1
      Also composed by: Alpert and Robinson.
    - Sweet Lorraine, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
    - Sweet Siamese, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 2712, side 1
    - Sweet Siamese, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 18546 A
    - (I Love You, I Love You, I Love You) Sweetheart of All My Dreams, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 811 H, side 1
      Also composed by: Lowe.
    - Sweetheart's Holiday, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 1074, side 1
      Also composed by: Robinson.
    - Te Prohibo el Cabaret = I Forbid You the Cabaret, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 40163 A
    - Ten Little Fingers and Ten Little Toes (Down in Tennessee), 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 3477, side 2
      Also composed by: Nelson.
    - That's Just My Way of Forgetting You, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 661 H, side 1
      Also composed by: Brown and Henderson.
    - To Each His Own, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 20 1921 A
    - Toodles, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 10269, side 2
    - Tuck Me to Sleep in My Old Kentucky Home, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 3465, side 2
      Also performed by: George Reardon.
    - Waitin' for the Evenin' Mail, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 12061 B
    - The Waltz I Can't Forget, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 827 H, side 1
      Also composed by: Kahn.
    - Waltzing Bugle Boy, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 1358, side 1
    - When Francis Dances With Me, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 3521, side 2
    - When the Moon Comes Over the Mountain, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 5359 C, side 1
      Also composed by: Woods and Johnson.
    - You Know You Belong to Somebody Else (So Why Don't You Leave Me Alone), 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 14513
    - You Put a Song in My Heart, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 20 1921 B
    - You'd Rather Forget Than Forgive, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 1187 b
    - You're Just an Armful of Love, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 1074, side 2
  - Jazz Recordings, Subseries 2.
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 264)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 265)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 266)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 267)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 268)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 269)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 270)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 271)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 272)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 273)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 274)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 306)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 307)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 308)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 309)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 310)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 311)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 312)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 313)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 314)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 315)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 316)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 317)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 318)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 319)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 320)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 321)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 322)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 323)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 324)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 325)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 326)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 327)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 328)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 329)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 330)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 331)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 332)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 333)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 334)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 335)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 336)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 337)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 338)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 2305)
  - Album Covers, Subseries 3.
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 765)
      Covers to recordings in Box 727
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 766)
      Covers to recordings in Box 728
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 767)
      Covers to recordings in Box 729
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 768)
      Covers to recordings in Box 730
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 769)
      Covers to recordings in Box 731
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 770)
      Covers to recordings in Box 732
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 771)
      Covers to recordings in Box 733
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 772)
      Covers to recordings in Box 734
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 773)
      Covers to recordings in Box 735
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 774)
      Covers to recordings in Box 736
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 775)
      Covers to recordings in Box 737
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 776)
      Covers to recordings in Box 738
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 777)
      Covers to recordings in Box 739
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 778)
      Covers to recordings in Box 740
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 779)
      Covers to recordings in Box 741
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 780)
      Covers to recordings in Box 742
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 781)
      Covers to recordings in Box 743
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 782)
      Covers to recordings in Box 744
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 783)
      Covers to recordings in Box 745
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 784)
      Covers to recordings in Box 746
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 785)
      Covers to recordings in Box 747
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 786)
      Covers to recordings in Box 748
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 787)
      Covers to recordings in Box 749
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 788)
      Covers to recordings in Box 750
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 789)
      Covers to recordings in Box 751
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 790)
      Covers to recordings in Box 752
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 791)
      Covers to recordings in Box 753
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 792)
      Covers to recordings in Box 754
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 793)
      Covers to recordings in Box 755
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 794)
      Covers to recordings in Box 756
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 795)
      Covers to recordings in Box 762
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 796)
      Covers to recordings in Box 763
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 797)
      Covers to recordings in Box 764
    - Assorted Album Covers (Box 804)
      Without 78's
  - Unprocessed Recordings, Subseries 4.
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 726)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 805)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 806)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 807)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 808)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 809)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 810)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 811)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 812)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 813)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 814)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 815)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 816)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 817)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 818)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 819)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 820)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 821)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 822)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 823)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 824)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 825)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 826)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 827)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 849)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 850)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 851)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 852)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 853)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 854)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 855)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 856)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 857)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 858)
      J. Berl Schwartz gift.
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 859)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 860)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 861)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 862)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 863)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 864)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 866)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 867)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 868)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 869)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 870)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 871)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 872)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 873)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 874)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 875)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 879)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 880)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 881)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 882)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 883)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 884)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 885)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 886)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 887)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 888)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 889)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 890)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 891)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 892)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 893)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 894)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 895)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 896)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 897)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 898)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 899)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 900)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 901)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 902)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 903)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 904)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 905)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 906)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 907)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 908)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 909)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 910)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 911)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 912)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 913)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 914)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 915)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 916)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 917)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 918)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 919)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 920)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 921)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 922)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 923)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 924)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 925)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 926)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 927)
    - Unprocessed Commercial Recordings (Box 928)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 929)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 930)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 931)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 932)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 933)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 934)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 935)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 936)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 937)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 938)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 939)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 940)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 942)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 943)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 954)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 956)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 973)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 974)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 975)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 976)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 977)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 978)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 979)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 980)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 981)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 982)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 983)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 984)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 985)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 986)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 987)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 988)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 989)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 990)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 991)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 992)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 993)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 994)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 995)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 996)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 997)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 998)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 999)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1000)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1001)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1002)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1003)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1004)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1005)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1006)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1007)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1008)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1009)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1010)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1012)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1013)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1014)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1015)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1016)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1017)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1018)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1019)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1020)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1021)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1022)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1023)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1024)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1025)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1026)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 1027)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 10111)
- Eselun Gift, Series 4.
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 966)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 967)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 968)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 969)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 970)
- Harry James Sound Recording Collection, Series 5.
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 944)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 945)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 946)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 947)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 948)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 949)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 950)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 951)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 952)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 953)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 955)
- Silbaugh Gift, Series 6.
  - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 300)
  - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 301)
  - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 302)
- Ken Stone Gift, Series 7.
  - 10-inch collection, Subseries 1.
    - Benny at the Ballroom
      Publisher no.: CL 2533
    - Bille Holiday: Vol. 1, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: c-135
    - Bing Crosby: A Collection of Early Recordings Volume 1, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: B-1012
    - Bix and the Wolverine Orchestra Chicago
      Publisher no.: JZTL 1001
      Vol. 1
    - Bix and Tram, 1947; 4 discs
      Publisher no.: c-1444
    - Boogie Woogie, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: C-44
      Artists: Meade Lux Lewis, Pete Johnson, Albert Ammons, Harry James Trio, Count Basie
    - Brunswick Collector's Series: Eddie Lang - Joe Venuti and their All Star Orchestra, 2 discs
      Publisher no.: B-1021
    - Date with the King
      Publisher no.: CL 2572
    - Dixie Land: Vol. 1
      Publisher no.: 5006a/b
      Treasury of Jazz Series
    - Dixieland Classics: Phil Napoleon's Emperors of Jazz Vol.1
      Publisher no.: MG 25078
      Artists: Phil Napoloen, Frank Sinorelli, Lou McGarrity, Tony Sprago, Felix Globe, Joe Dixon, Chuck Wayne.
    - Dixieland Classics: Phil Napoleon's Masters of Jazz Vol. 2
      Publisher no.: MG25079
      Artists: Phil Napoleon, Frank Signorelli, Lou McGarrity, Tony Sprago, Felix Globe, Joe Dixon, Chuck Wayne.
    - Duke Ellington Panorama, A, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: P-138
    - From Austin High Comes Jazz: by Budd Freeman and his Famous Chicagoans, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: C-40
    - Gems of Jazz: Vol. 1, 6 discs 18m series
      Publisher no.: Album no. 200
      Artists: Mildred Bailey, Bunny Berigan, Pete Brown, Benny Carter, Cozy Cole, Eddie Condon, Israel Crosby, Bud Freeman, Bobby Hackett, Johnny Hodges, Gene Krupa, Villy Kyle, Mead "Lux" Lewis, Joe Marsala, Grachan Moncur, Jess Stacy, Claude Thornhill, Teddy Wilson
    - Getting Sentimental with Tommy Dorsey, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: P80-5
    - Glenn Miller
      Publisher no.: LPM 31
    - Hackett's Horn
      Publisher no.: 202
      Artists: George Brunis, Sterling Rose, Pee Wee Russell, Ernie Caceres, Flyod O'Brien, Eddie Condon, Dave Bowman, Frankie Carle.
    - Hot Jazz by McKinney's Cotton Pickers [cover], 4 discs
      Artists: Bunny Berigan and his Boys, Louis Armstrong and his Orchestra, Andre Andre Kostelanetz
    - Hot Jazz Classics: Dorsey Brothers, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: C-51
    - Hot Jazz Classics: Hot Trombones, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: C-46
      Artists: Jay C. Higginbotham, Jimmy Harrison, Jack Teagarden, Benny Morton, Floyd O'Brien, Miff Mole.
    - Hot Jazz Classics: Louis and Earl, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: C-73
    - Hot Jazz Classics: Teddy Wilson-Billie Holiday, 1935; 4 discs
      Publisher no.: C-61
    - Hot Jazz: Louis Armstrong
      Artists: Bix Biederbeck and his gang, Louis Armstrong and Orchestra.
    - Hot Trumpets, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: C-66
      Artists: Bix Beiderbecke, Red Nichols, Muggsy Spanier, Cootie Williams, Louis Armstrong, Henry Allen, Joe Smith, Buck Clayton
    - Ike Quebec [cover], 3 discs
      Artists: Frank Teschmacher avec Miff Mole et son Orchestre, Bix Beiderbecke avec Frankie Trumbauer et son Orchestra, Sydney Bechet and his New Orleans Feetwarmers, Tommy Dorsey and his Orchestra
    - Jazz Concert at Eddie Condon's, 1946; 4 discs
      Publisher no.: A-490
    - Jazz Concert: George Gershwin, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: A-298
      featuring Lee Wiley
    - Jazztone Society: Jazz Sampler
      Publisher no.: J-Spec 100
      Artists: Sidney Bechet and his New Orleans Feetwarmers, REd Norvo All Stars, Charlie PArker All Stars, Art Tatum TRio, Buck Clayton Quintent, Coleman Hawkins Quartet, Jack Teagarden and his Orchestra, Erroll Garner Trio, Woody Herman Woodchoppers, Rex Stewart and his Dixieland Jazz Band